https://www.onthehouse.com/privacy-policy/

Don't Miss
Have a home improvement question? Call our radio show at 1-800-737-2474 anytime!
Effective date: October 07, 2018
On the House Media (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.onthehouse.com/ website (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.onthehouse.com/
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address
First name and last name
Phone number
Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
On the House Media uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
On the House Media will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
On the House Media may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of On the House Media
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
AdRotate
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By email: info@careybros.com
Latest News
Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree
“Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree” Show Notes...
Posted December 5, 2020
0
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
As if shopping for men isn’t already hard enough, welcome...
Posted December 4, 2020
0
Healthy Winter Home
This winter, make sure you have a healthy home with...
Posted December 4, 2020
0
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Trees.com, the online authority for hydroponics, gardening advice, product reviews,...
Posted December 1, 2020
0
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Greenery? Stockings? Lights? Decorating interior stairway systems can take many...
Posted December 1, 2020
0
Two-Tone Mouldings Add Holiday Sparkle to Homes
Get ready to add some new sparkle throughout your home...
Posted November 27, 2020
0
I Feel My Temperature Rising
Thank you for tuning in to learn how to heat...
“Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree” Show...
December 5, 2020
0
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
As if shopping for men isn’t already hard enough,...
December 4, 2020
0
Healthy Winter Home
This winter, make sure you have a healthy home...
December 4, 2020
0
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Trees.com, the online authority for hydroponics, gardening advice, product...
December 1, 2020
0
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Greenery? Stockings? Lights? Decorating interior stairway systems can take...
December 1, 2020
0
The Pressures On Giveaway
The Pressures On Giveaway with Briggs & Stratton This...
August 15, 2015
46
The Tools That “Rock” Giveaway
Everyone loves tools. If you’re performance-minded do-it-yourselfer or the...
March 20, 2015
27
The Carey Brother’s Great Backyard Makeover Sweepstakes
Enter to Win $1,000 Visa gift card and over...
May 27, 2016
25
Shawn says:
I don't see notes about using vinegar in a di...
John says:
On the Feb 8 broadcast you mentioned two item...
Neal Kinder says:
I went on to Chemcore website and could not l...
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Simpson Strong-Tie Launches Eight-Episode Video Series for Contractors and Homeowners on How to Build a Stronger Deck
Homeowner DIY Extreme: Creating Faux Brick on Home Exterior
Garage Doors: Little Changes Make a Big Difference
Focus on Handling Fuel Safely During National Safety Month
Infographics
When you can’t find a stud in the wall [Infographic]
17 Haas Door 700 Series Steel Doors Installed at Brooklawn Country Club
All-Glass Garage Doors Trending High for Homeowners
Design & Decor
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Simpson Strong-Tie Launches Eight-Episode Video Series for Contractors and Homeowners on How to Build a Stronger Deck
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
Healthy Winter Home
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
Healthy Winter Home
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
Healthy Winter Home
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
17 Haas Door 700 Series Steel Doors Installed at Brooklawn Country Club
All-Glass Garage Doors Trending High for Homeowners
Recalls
Recall: Black & Decker Recalls Hammer Drills Due to Injury Hazard
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
Healthy Winter Home
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
Healthy Winter Home
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
Tips on Decorating Interior Stairways for the Holidays
Back Under the On The House Christmas Tree
2020 Gifts for Guys Guide
Healthy Winter Home
Trees.com Announces 14 Best Artificial Christmas Trees of 2020
